#### **KAYLEM BILLETT CV**

#### KAYLEM BILLETT

#

#### **KEYNSHAM**

#

Email: kaylembillett@hotmail.co.uk Mobile: #

## **PROFILE**

Highly motivated and enthusiastic graduate with many years of experience within work-based environments, with an advanced knowledge of computing gathered via an applied computing degree from Bath University. Throughout my degree I studied various software development methods but specialised in website design and development. I am very keen to develop these skills through self-learning and a professional environment.

## COMPETENCIES

- Delivering at pace and working in pressured situations with limited timeframes throughout my threeyear degree.
- A thirst for developing and building on existing skills and competencies independently and though University and paid jobs. Actively embracing change and continuous improvement.
- Lots of experience and working with and providing real world software solutions for clients ensuring a Customer focus always.
- Studied a very wide variety of modules within different aspects of computing, giving me a broad knowledge of the Industry.
- Enjoy teamworking and supporting others to meet Customers' demands.
- Highly focussed and always trying to deliver a quality product on time. Delivering on my promises.

# **EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS**

2017-2018 Bath University

## **BSc (Hons) in Applied Computing**

59.6% (2:2)

- Advanced web-based technologies 66%
- Introduction to managing financial and non-financial resources 62%
- Managing marketing activities 65%
- Managing performance 62%
- Developing technologies 59%
- Multi-tasking systems 62%
- Research methods 65%
- Work-based research project 55%
- Creative computing 60%
- Managing information 48%

2015 – 2017 Bath University

Foundation degree in Science in Applied Computing Merit

2013 - 2015 City of Bath College

BTEC Level 3 extended diploma in Information Technology Merit, Merit, Merit

2011 - 2013 Ralph Allen School, Bath

6 GCSE's Grades (A-D)

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2018 – Present	the City Pub Group Plc	Bartender	10 Months
2014 – 2018	Dine with style	FOH catering, Bar work, Chef assistant	4 Years
2013-2014	Argos	Sales team	8 Months
2011-2012	Rotork	IT helpdesk Assistant	1 week

## **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

## Data analyst - B&NES

51+ hour Gold Volunteering Award presented by the high sheriff of Somerset for assisting in the analysis of data for the B&NES Cyberbullying Research project.

# **OTHER ACHEIVEMENTS - TRAVELLING**

- Recently independent travelling experience to Thailand, Vietnam, Cambodia and Laos (Jan Apr 2019)
- Many new skills developed: people skills; working and living in diverse cultures overseas; appreciation for other cultures, behaviours, and ways of life.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

## **Programming Languages**

- HTML (24+ months)
- CSS (24+ months)
- JavaScript (6+ months)
- C++ (6+ months)

- C# (6+ months)
- PHP (12+ months)
- MySQL (12+ months)
- Git (3+ months)

# **Programming Frameworks**

- Bootstrap (12+ months)
- jQuery (6+ months)
- Ruby on Rails (6+ months)

## **INTERESTS**

- Enjoy playing for a local 11 a side football team, training Wednesdays and competitive games on Sundays.
- I enjoy following current and developing technologies through online articles and magazines.
- Keen interest in playing video games and follow various professional Esports teams.
- I enjoy following/engaging in various creative arts (music, graphic design, street arts).

## REFEREES

Name: Paul Long Name: Tom Lovell

Address: # Address: #

Mobile Number: # Mobile Number: #